Guide to the George and Louise Spindler Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers
  - ED270D-Syllabus Educ. In Cross-Cultural Perspective, 1991 Spring (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Family Case Study File, 1957 January 13-1978 January 31 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Greenfield, Sidney, 1967 February 14-1975 February 18 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Peters/Bedouin?, 1960 November 28-1970 February 10 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Spindler-Fisher?, 1966 July 9-1973 May 5 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Tefft, Stanton-Shoshoni, 1967 May 29-1969 December 26 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - No definite decision as yet, 1969 December 5-1974 March 15 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - These People Have Said "No", 1970 April 1-1971 November 13 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Basic Anthropology Unit-General, 1969 November 14-1973 January 8 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Rohners-Socialization, 1969 December 12-1973 July 9 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Downs; War and Peace, 1970 April 1-1971 November 5 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Friedl-Sex Roles Small Community in Mass Society, 1969 December 22-1973 January 23 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Gamst, Fred B.A.U. (Peasants), 1969 December 5-1973 March 27 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Hicks, George L., 1968 January 23-1975 June 17 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Untitled, 1971 November 15-1972 August 17 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Kearney, Michael, 1972 June 26-1973 October 17 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Keiser: Urban Anthropology, 1970 January 9-1975 March 24 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Untitled, 1972 February 20-1974 June 24 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Middleton, John B.A.U. (Social Structure), 1969 November 25-1972 August 15 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Norbeck: Religion (?), 1969 December 3-1975 February 13 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Schusky: Kinship, 1970 December 23-1974 July 16 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1970 December 9-1973 April 18 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Chronological File, 1972 March 17-1977 November 22 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Untitled, 1968 November 12-1975 November 30 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Floyd, Lois G., 1975 September 16-1977 January 5 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Hicks, George L. BAU?, 1975 October 19 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Louise Spindler - Revised BAU on Culture Change, 1976 May 31 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - MacCannel, Dean, 1974 April 4-1975 November 5 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Untitled, 1975 December 1-1977 January 31 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Otterbein, Keith, 1969 May 23-1974 December 23 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Case Studies - Wm. L. Partridge, 1976 March 26-1978 March 28 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Case Studies-Revisions, 1976 February 27-1978 March 28 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Prospective Case Studies (possibilities), 1976 June 15-1978 March 28 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Prospective Case Studies (possibilities), 1975 September 9-1976 November 15 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - New Prospects (other than Case Studies), 1975 May 12-1977 March 23 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - PUBLICATIONS--OTHER THAN BAU'S AND CASE STUDIES (Prospective), 1975 August 7-1978 March 28 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Peshkin, Alan-Growing Up American: The Intimate World of a Rural School and Community, 1975 March 12-1976 October 19 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Willy Pilcher-The Cultural Study of Urban People and Urban Places, 1976 January 25-1976 March 4 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, 1975 September 17-1976 October 19 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - CORRESPONDENCE-General, 1975 September 10-1977 March 10 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - CORRESPONDENCE-PROFESSIONAL (Non-HRW), 1975 September 171979 February 13 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - George D. Spindler-Personal Correspondence, 1976 March 17-1977 April 18 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Spindlers-correspondence with them, 1977 April 26-December 18 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Geo. and Louise Spindler - Correspondence to and from HOME OFFICE (during sabbaticals, etc.), Undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - g + L. Biographies. ORIGINALS, Undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Photos, Undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Biography G+LS, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - George Spindler - CV, Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Instrumental Activities Inventory-extra copies, Undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - DEPARTMENT (Anthropology) - Administration, Personnel, etc, 1975 September 30-1976 October 14 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence-General, 1975 September 9-1976 May 3 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Louise S. Spindler-Curriculum Vitae, Undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Course Materials, 1979 Winter (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Course Materials, 1979 Spring (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Recommendations-Colleagues and Others, 1975 October 18-1977 November 22 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Untitled, 1975 October 19-1976 November 24 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - HRW-GENERAL (Accounting, etc), 1975 December 17-1976 March 26 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - HRW-CORRESPONDENCE-Professional (of interest to HRW), 1975 September 8-1976 October 19 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - NIH, 1972 February-June (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION RESEARCH GRANT APPLICATION, 1976 September 22 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - RESEARCH FUNDS-Applications for Grants + Correspondence, 1976 January 27-1979 February 15 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 1976 November 22 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - NIH Research Grant Application, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - NSF Grant Info, 1976 May 3-August 31 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - The Making of Psychological Anthropology-Correspondence, 1975 October 19-1977 March 23 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Psychological-Anthropology Text, 1973 July 22-1975 February 26 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Spiro, Melford Psycholog. Anthrop., 1974 March 11-1976 March 26 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Recollections of Frank Spindler By His Son, 1977 March (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - George D. Spindler-Change and Continuity in American Core Cultural Values: An Anthropological Perspective, Undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Adaptations to the Study of Change-by Geo. and Louise Spindler (for Goldschmidt UCLA Retirement) (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Reviews and/or Evaluations-by Geo. or Louise Spindler, 1975 October 20-1977 September 30 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Course Critiques for Cultural Transmission Course, 1982 Winter (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Course Critiques for Social and Cultural Anthropology Course, 1987 Autumn (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Course Critiques for Anthro 280 Course, 1985 Summer (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Course Critiques for Anthro 280 Course, 1986 Spring (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Course Critiques for Ethnography of Schooling Course, 1983 Summer (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Course Critiques for Anthro 280 Course, 1986 Summer (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Course Critiques for Anthropology of American Culture, 1983 Winter (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Course Critiques for Ethnography and Schooling Course, 1982 Summer (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Course Critiques for Ethnographic Method Course, 1987 Summer (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Course Critiques for American Culture Course, 1987 Autumn (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Course Critiques for Anthropological Perspectives on America Course, 1979 Autumn (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Course Critiques for Anthropological Perspectives on American Culture, 1983 Summer (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Course Critiques for Cultural Transmission Course, 1982 Summer (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Course Critiques for Anthropological Perspectives on American Culture Course, 1981 Winter (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Course Critiques for Cultural Transmission Course, 1981 Winter (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Course Critiques for Anthropological Perspectives Course, 1978 Spring (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Course Critiques for Native North America Course, 1980 Spring (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Course Critiques for American Culture Course, 1980 Spring (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Course Critiques for Ethnography of Schooling Course, 1979 Summer (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Course Critiques for Anthropological Perspectives on American Culture, 1979 Winter (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Course Critiques for Cultural Transmission Course, 1980 Summer (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Course Critiques for Cultural Transmission Course, 1984 Spring (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Course Critiques for Social and Cultural Anthropology Course, 1983 Winter (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Course Critiques for Anthropological Perspectives on American Culture and Intro. To, 1984 Winter (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Course Critiques for Native North Americans Course, 1986 Winter (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Course Critiques for Ethnography and Schooling Course, 1985 Summer (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Course Critiques for Anthropological Perspectives on American Culture Course, 1985 Summer (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Introduction to sociocultural anthropology (Anthro 001/101) - course materials, 1976-1991 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Anthropological perspectives on American culture (Anthro 015/116)-course materials, 1983-1987 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Native North America (Anthro 102)-course materials, 1980-1986 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Ethnography of schooling (Anthro 214/Ed280)-course materials, 1980-1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Cultural transmission (Anthro 266)-course materials, 1980-1991 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Assorted anthropology course materials, 1964-1991 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Education as cultural transmission-outlines, guidelines for case studies, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Criteria for a good ethnography, Undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Case studies on aspects of American culture-list, Undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Course critiques: social and cultural anthropology, 1979 Spring (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Photographs-Native Americans (Canada, U.S.), 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Postcards-Australian aboriginal ceremonies, Undated (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, possibly from China, Undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Maps: Canada, North American Indians, Top of the World, Undated (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Phelan proposal (memoranda regarding), 1978 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - American Anthropological Association-brochures, 1967-1990 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Textor, Bob-letter and proposal, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Schooling in Schonhausen-reports, Undated (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Mailing receipts, petty cash receipts, 1970-1974 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Spindlers, typescript papers and articles, 1963-1984 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Spindlers, reprints, 1952-1984 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified survey/test responses, Undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - A155 TAT responses, Undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Edgerton, Robert-Study of deviance, Undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Wax, Rosalie-Fieldwork as education, Undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Anderson-Levitt, Kathryn-What's French about French teachers' view of the classroom?, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Henry, Mary E.-Private schools and the hidden curriculum, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Stanford in Germany-notes, miscellaneous papers, Undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - NSF and OE proposal-Educational and cultural adaptation in an urbanizing rural German village, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - German national character-notes, 1968-1970 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Drug culture of Burgbach, student paper by Charlie Skromer, Thom Merrell, and Les Bush, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Educational and cultural adaptation in an urbanizing rural German village-survey results, Undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Educational and cultural adaptation in an urbanizing rural German village-survey results, Undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Educational and cultural adaptation in an urbanizing rural German village-completed survey forms (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Educational and cultural adaptation in an urbanizing rural German village-completed survey forms (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Educational and cultural adaptation in an urbanizing rural German village-pictures used in the study (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - I.A.I. additional parent sample (Strumpfelbach), Undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - German village study-student paper and quantitative notes, Undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - German village study-summations and notes, Undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - German village study-qualitative, 6th grade, Beutelsbach, Undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - German village study-qualitative, 7th grade, VE, Undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - German village study-qualitative, 8th grade, Undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - German village study-qualitative, 9th grade, Undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - German village study-qualitative, 5A and 5B, Undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - German village study-chart, Undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - German village study-completed survey forms, Undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - German village study-completed survey forms, Undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - German village study-completed survey forms, Undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Course critiques-Anthro 001, 1976 Winter (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Computer printouts, Undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Audio visual materials-videos, audio tapes, film, overhead projection sheets, Undated (Box 54)